A fugitive from a killer. A remote outpost. A fight to the death.
Legionnaire is a action, war, adventure film directed by Peter MacDonald.
Alain Lefevre is a boxer paid by a Marseille mobster to take a dive.
When he wins the fight he attempts to flee to America
with the mobster's girlfriend Katrina.
This plan fails and he seeks escape by joining the foreign legion.
As part of the legion he tangles with abusive lieutenant Steinkampf and
bonds with legionnaires Luther, Mackintosh and Rosetti.
Alain Lefevre, played by Jean-Claude Van Damme.
Luther, played by Adewale Akinnuoye-Agbaje.
Sgt. Steinkampf, played by Steven Berkoff.
Mackintosh, played by Nicholas Farrell.
Lucien Galgani, played by Jim Carter.
Katarina, played by Ana Sofrenović.
Legionnaire is a 1998 American drama war film directed by Peter MacDonald and starring Jean-Claude Van Damme as a 1920s boxer
who wins a fight after he was hired by gangsters to lose it and then flees to join the French Foreign Legion.
The cast includes Adewale Akinnuoye-Agbaje, Daniel
Caltagirone, Nicholas Farrell, and Steven Berkoff.
The film was filmed in Morocco at  Tangier and Ouarzazate.
The film explores themes of shepherd, martial arts,
rebel, morocco, foreign legionaire.